Okay.
Check, check.
Are we running? Are we hot? Okay.
This is a meeting to suss out the
requirements.
For my capstone project for accelerated
engineering with GitHub Copilot,
I am looking to design a game.
For my four-year-old son,
he is turning 4 next Monday.
I want something.
That.
He would enjoy to play.
where he can grasp the controls quickly
and that has good replay value.
So I think it should be somewhat simple.
challenging enough for him because he is
smart and he loves video games.
He plays a lot of video games.
And obviously,
it must be doable within the time frame
that we're using this agentic workflow.
So the first thing I thought about was...
doing a little game around a scooter.
So he wants a little like razor scooter.
And he wants to be able to ride his
scooter to the Wallingford playfield
where he plays at the park.
He meets his friends there. Him being 4,
he obviously can't do this on his own.
His mom and I.
Um...
take him to the park and even with his
scooter,
he would be riding to the park with us.
But I thought there could be a game where
he could ride to the park.
in the game by himself.
Maybe he has to collect an item like a
helmet,
or maybe he has a helmet in the game
already.
I should emphasize that my son is wearing
a helmet while he's riding a scooter.
So when he's playing the game,
he gets that idea.
So we need to decide the technology,
the platform.
Is it going to be what tech stacks we're
going to use?
How we're going to go about creating some
simple goals for him and how he can
replay it once he meets some challenges.
So there should be...
There should be a goal.
It should involve his scooter and he
should win the game by getting to the
park and meeting his friends.
There can be other.
ways to do this,
as long as it's scooter themed,
like if he races his friends on a scooter
or something,
something simple like that as well.
So that's where we're going to end this.
We need to come up with a good scooter
game for my son,
and then we will start picking
technologies.